Hilary Knight Papers 1992.0047
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series III: Published Articles Illustrated by Hilary Knight, 1973-1997
  - Cricket Magazine, 1973 November - 1997 October
    - Vol. 12: no. 12, 1985 August (Box 16, Folder 272)
    - Vol. 13: no. 3, 1985 November (Box 16, Folder 273)
    - Vol. 13: no. 5, 1986 January (Box 16, Folder 274)
    - Vol. 13: no. 9, 1986 May (Box 16, Folder 275)
    - Vol. 14: no. 1, 1986 September (Box 16, Folder 276)
    - Vol. 14: no. 4, 1986 December (Box 16, Folder 277)
    - Vol. 14: no. 7, 1987 March (Box 16, Folder 278)
    - Vol. 15: no. 1, 1987 September (Box 16, Folder 279)
    - Vol. 15: no. 2, 1987 October (Box 16, Folder 280)
    - Vol. 15: no. 5, 1988 January (Box 16, Folder 281)
    - Vol. 16: no. 2, 1988 October (Box 16, Folder 282)
    - Vol. 16: no. 5, 1989 January (Box 16, Folder 283)
    - Vol. 17: no. 12, 1990 August (Box 16, Folder 284)
    - Vol. 18: no. 5, 1991 January (Box 16, Folder 285)
    - Vol. 19: no. 5, 1992 January (Box 16, Folder 286)
    - Vol. 20: no. 9, 1993 May (Box 16, Folder 287)
    - Vol. 21: no. 1, 1993 September (Box 16, Folder 288)
    - Vol. 25: no. 2, 1997 October (Box 16, Folder 289)
  - Lady Bug Magazine, 1989-1997
    - Published articles (7), 1990-1997 (Box 17, Folder 297)
    - Finished artwork, undated, 1989-1993 (Box 17, Folder 298)
  - Spider Magazine, 1995, 1997
    - Published magazines (2), 1995 December, 1997 February (Box 17, Folder 296)
- Series IV: Unpublished Works, undated
  - Fleet Footed Florence, undated
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 130)
    - Book dummy (text only), undated (Box 8, Folder 131)
    - Sketches, undated (Box 8, Folder 135)
- Series V: Promotional Materials, 1976-2001
  - Algonquin Cat, 1980-2001
    - Cards (3), 1980 November 10, 1980 December, 2001
      Includes collection notes from Hilary Knight, [2001?].
  - Eloise, 1955-1995
    - 40th Anniversary poster, 1955-1995 (Box 18, Folder 303)
      Signed "For Nora + Norman Stevens From Hilary Knight"
  - Screamy Mimi, 1987, 1991
    - Artwork (matted) used at UConn Book Fair, 1987, 1991 October
  - Ten Tall Soldiers, 1991
    - Poster, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 301)
  - That Makes Me Mad!, 1976
    - Publishing advertisement, 1976 February (Box 9, Folder 171)